Hi, this is Liz Muller from Liz's Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip we're going to show you how to deal with dry, damaged hair.
Now this hair is pretty nice, and it's nice and soft, and it doesn't have any damage to it.
But damaged hair would usually look frizzy, it would have the split ends on it.
You can see it a mile away.
It doesn't have anything to it, it's just really hair that looks like it's hurting.
And the way you want to condition that hair is you might want to use something that moisturizes the hair, a moisturizing mask.
Do it once a week.
Maybe get a product that you can use every time you shampoo your hair, and leave it on about ten to fifteen minutes, OK, because you want to get the hair back and restored.
If it's way too damaged, you know, don't be afraid to clip it off.
Sometimes you have to cut off the hair because it's just way damaged, and it doesn't have any repair.
But now-a-day's, we have such wonderful products out there, that I'm sure you might be able to find something out there to condition the hair and make it the way you had it before, or at least close to it.
This is Liz Muller, and this is how to deal with dry, damaged hair.